This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Separated from the rest of his crew,
Luffy has finally arrived at Marineford to rescue his brother Ace.
With Jinbei's help, he cleared the encircling walls an inch closer to the scaffold.
He continues his progress towards Ace as the battle between the Whitebeard Pirates and Navy rages on in the plaza.
Son of a...
The ravages of time humble us all.
Yes, even you.
Screw the fight, this is what I was afraid of.
Huh, wouldn't turn your back on me if I were you.
Marco!
You gonna make the same mistake?
Someone has to see you off.
And that duty seems to have fallen on me.
Mops, no!
As long as I do everything I can, I don't care if I die.
I'm begging you, you have to let me fight!
If I don't keep fighting...
And they kill Ace cause I wasn't there for him...
Then I'd rather be dead anyway!
Right now!
It's the only fight that matters, live or die!
Or die!
Oh, fine!
It's your life!
Give us a good show!
Lucy...
To live up to a promise, Luffy and Kobe collide!
Ugh, this is ridiculous.
What could possibly take so long?
I'm back, sir! Sorry for the wait!
These two replacements should be able to carry out the execution, sir!
Alright, fine! Hurry and get up here then!
Right!
Remember, straw boy!
Energy hormone may get you pumped for now!
But if you fall again, that's it!
You're a dead boy!
Got it?
Energy hormone only tricks your body into thinking you're okay!
It's not actually healing your injuries at all!
That's alright.
In that case...
I just won't fall again!
Huh?
Well, don't kill yourself too badly!
Crap! It's happening!
Hold on a sec!
You're not executing Ace while I'm around!
The kid's crazy!
But it isn't like he's going to change his mind under these circumstances!
Guess I might as well give him some backup then!
Hold on, straw boy!
Eve is coming for you!
He's over there!
Straw Hat's still alive!
Not for long, he's not!
He's not!
Move it! I've got him!
I'll finish him off!
Enough crap!
You're not taking another step!
We've got you surrounded now!
Yeah, he's right! There's no way you can defeat all of us!
The navy always wins!
You might as well give up!
Ha ha ha!
Crap!
You're not taking another step!
We've got you surrounded now!
Yeah, he's right! There's no way you can defeat all of us!
The navy always wins!
You might as well give up!
Up!
Incoming!
Death, we come!
My, what a fanciful strike!
Thanks, Eva, I owe you!
Luffy?
Are you gonna fight?
Kobe!
I see it now.
I decided long ago that I'm gonna be king of the pirates.
If I have to die fighting for that, then I die.
If I put my mind to it, if I'm prepared to die for it, could I do something like that?
Like what?
Do you think...
Do you think I could ever join the Marines?
Marines?
Yes! Catching bad guys is the only thing I've ever wanted to do!
It's been my dream since I was a child!
If Luffy and I had never met back then, I couldn't have made it this far.
Alright, focus.
If I want any hope of growing stronger as a Marine...
I have to fight all enemies, no matter who they are.
This is war!
I'm sorry, Luffy, but I'm gonna have to kill you!
Aaaaahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!!!
Now shave!
Because I promised myself, that I'll keep trying...
because i promised myself that i'll keep trying till till i become a marine admiral
no i'm sorry i got carried away this is so embarrassing i just want to dig a hole and
bury my head in it that was really arrogant of me i got worked up after seeing you again and i just
obi you said you're gonna fight me right then you will become that strong you'll have to
yeah but a marine admiral next time i see you we're gonna be stronger too a whole lot stronger
i don't get it
i just blurted out some ridiculous dream something i don't even have a right to follow
but he didn't laugh he believed in me
looks like i got carried away again
i'm useless after all i guess it's back to the truck bard hey kobe
peace
i knew again those dirty frauds impersonating my friend monkey d luffy
why can't they just move
hey what do you think you're doing boah hancock one of the seven warlords
navy ally detected ceasing attack oh yeah you guys are on the same side thanks a bunch hancock
isn't that the pirate empress have you two got a thing going on i should know about he said it
he said my name and he didn't get it wrong but of course how could i
shower me in sweet gratitude my love you have my thanks yes oh and hancock yes
i owe you my life yes boa hancock
please move you are standing in the way
i never gave you permission to address me in such a manner
is that it magma brat
hold on pops i'm coming to save you
wow it went straight through take a few more of these and have yourself a nice long rest okay
yeah just try and stop me ah well that certainly throws a wrinkle into my plan regeneration huh
so that must be why they call you the phoenix hey give me a hand will you
see prism stone
oh it hurt that time huh
they got joezu too he's frozen solid
that's two commanders down what should we do now take out the head and the body will follow
the
he's in danger
hold still you monster
you fool i will not be chained good now close in fast
but give the others an attack white breed with all you've got
uh
We'll save him!
No! Stay back!
You punks really think that's all it takes to defeat me?
Just a few toy swords and guns?
I could tear you all apart single-handedly, but you know that, don't you?
Because you quake when you hear the name Whitebeard!
Whitebeard!
Ah!
Ah!!
Fuck!
Th-That's insane!
This is our chance! Quickly, before he recovers!
Everybody, follow me!
Sir!
What did he say?
That's a good one!
I don't need to recover from a scratch like this!
You think this will stop me?
That I'll lie down and give up?
I'm not such a fool!
I know what will happen if I falter, even for a moment!
What will happen if I die?
And knowing that cold truth, I can't allow myself to submit, not until the bitter end!
So I'll wait until I've taken care of the future for my sons!
Got it, Ace?
Nice!
Oh, Pops!
Ah! Old fools lost it!
What the hell?
Oh!
Damn! And we were so close, too!
Bastards informed a barrier around Whitebeard's back!
You want us to bury you with the old man?!
Your mockery does not sway my honor!
It is our pride and our joy to stand beside him!
You bunch of fools!
Get away!
Pops!
What are your orders, Captain?
Shouldn't we go help defend Pops, too?
Captain Squad, where are you going?
Don't follow me.
You've done well, but a cowardly traitor such as myself must face his punishment.
Concerned about the future?
I'll be more than happy to show it to you now.
Let's end this.
Execute him!
Ace!
I'm too slow!
Don't make me laugh!
You think I can't stop those ruts from doing it?
From the start, this was the only way!
Ace!
Don't you dare!
It's not over yet!
Did you just do what I think you did?
It's the Conqueror's spirit.
Well, damn. This is a mess.
There's a surprise for you.
Why that little brat?
Unaware of his own power, Luffy unleashes the Conqueror's spirit, temporarily halting Ace's execution.
The Navy, now recognizing the threat he poses, sends all of their forces after him.
Thankfully, Ivankov has a plan that may forge a path to Ace.
On the next, One Piece! The scaffold at last! The way to Ace has opened!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!